#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ technicaldocumenter (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Basics of Salsforce Admin
Conga Revenue Lifecycle Cloud
X-Author for Contracts

### Languages

Hindi

English

Gujarati

#### Certifications

Understanding Confluence for users, managers and admins

ISO 9001:2015 QMS Internal Auditor Learn API Technical Writing - JSON and XML for Writers

Learn API Technical Writing 2: REST for Writers

# Vaishali S.

Technical Writer | Information Developer | Software Product Documenter | Creative Product Photographer

Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

# Summary

I am a seasoned software technical writer with 7+ years of experience in US HealthCare and Telecommunication domains. As a Technical Writer, I create and modify documents like online help, user guide, procedural manual, installation guide, operation and maintenance guide, troubleshooting guide, training material, admin guide, API documentation, and release note.

## Skill Highlights:

- Ability to simplify and present complex technical processes in layman's terms
- Understanding of concepts such as topic-based writing and topic reusability
- Basic knowledge of GitHub, Markdown, Jekyll, Swagger, and Postman
- Basic knowledge of wireframing and prototyping
- Ability to demonstrate software products to internal and external stockholders
- Internal as well as external coordination and communication
- Domains handled: US Healthcare IT and Telecommunication
- Methodology: Agile, DDLC, and SDLC
- Authoring and Editing Tools: Adobe RoboHelp, Atlassian
   Confluence, Microsoft Office, Adobe Photoshop, and TechSmith
   Snagit
- Project Management/ Tracking tools: Team Foundation Server and Atlassian JIRA
- Wireframing and Prototyping tools: Balsamiq, Draw.io, and InVision App

#technicalwriter #technicaldocumentation #softwaredocumentation #technicalwriting #microsoftword #healthcaredocumentation #telecommunication #informationdeveloper #APIdocumentation #docsascode #RESTapidocumentation

## Experience

Conga Sr Technical Writer April 2023 - Present (9 months)

STL - Sterlite Technologies Limited Senior Technical Writer September 2020 - March 2023 (2 years 7 months) Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

- Software Product Documentation
- Training Documentation

AssureCare LLC
Technical Writer
January 2019 - August 2020 (1 year 8 months)
Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

FKA iPatientCare Pvt. Ltd.

iPatientCare
Technical Writer
March 2016 - December 2018 (2 years 10 months)
Ahmedabad Area, India

Key Responsibilities:

- Created pre-release note, release note, online help, user manuals, installation guides, implementation guides, how-to guides, API documentation, FAQs, quick reference guides, training manuals, demo presentations, etc. for various healthcare software products (i.e., EMR, EHR, EPP, Telemedicine, RCM,

Medical Billing)

- Created supporting documentation for the "ONC Health IT" and "HL7 FHIR" certifications
- Created documentation for the CMS Quality reporting
- Collaborated with SMEs, Developers, Testers, and Support teams to procure relevant information and

ensure timely delivery of the documentation

 Participated in software design meetings to review design options and recommend alternatives based
 On User Experience and Industry Standards

Page 2 of 3

- Delivered product training within the organization

Revival Pixel - Unzip Absolute Quality

Manager Business Development | Business Proposal writer | Business Analyst

August 2014 - February 2016 (1 year 7 months)

Ahmedabad Area, India

#### Key Responsibilities:

- Involved in international business development
- Created technical project proposals and pitches for a global consumer base
- Involved in requirement analysis, workflow diagram, wire-framing, prototyping, and user acceptance testing
- Prepared post-go-live support documents
- Provided the first level of support after the project go-live

Engineering Consultancy
Consulting Engineer
October 2011 - July 2014 (2 years 10 months)
Gandhinagar, Gujarat

#### Key Responsibilities:

- Participated in business development, CRM, voice & non-voice sales, and developing market exposure
- Prepared technical proposals and tender documents for various projects
- Created technical data sheets, user guides, installation manuals, and other related documents for various

instruments/equipment

- Developed and maintained templates for marketing collateral

## Education

**Gujarat University** 

BE, Engineering · (2007 - 2011)